<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogsite on © Prantik Choudhary</title>
    <link>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogsite on © Prantik Choudhary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 11:25:05 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Article I: Dior x Air Jordan 1</title>
      <link>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blogs/blogs/chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blogs/blogs/chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>Christian Dior and Nike Air Jordan collaborated together to create one of the most expensive sneaker of all time,the “Air Dior 1’s”.They were officially debuted at the pre fall Miami show in 2020. The low version of these shoes were even advertised by Travis Scott in his Instagram.The high top version of these shoes are limited to only 8,500 pairs and the low tops are limited to 4,700 pairs.These shoes are designed under the supervision of designer Kim Jones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Article II: AMIRI</title>
      <link>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blogs/blogs/chapter-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blogs/blogs/chapter-5/</guid>
      <description>Stating the real facts,I have’nt been lucky enough yet to get my hands on any of the apparels be it jeans,sneakers,sweatshirts,jackets .etc. made by Amiri but this is amongst one of my favourite apparel brand that I have been following for a long time now. Mike Amiri is the creative director of this amazing clothing line and he made this from scratch,all the initial designs are made by him. The garment inherently costs more to make than other branded clothes hence they sell for a much higher price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Article III: Goyard</title>
      <link>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blogs/blogs/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blogs/blogs/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>Forget Louis Vuitton,Goyard is the new status symbol for the rich.Goyard bags are nowadays generally made on special orders.The special orders are entirely handmade in Goyard workshops.Goyard has its boutiques located in NYC,London,Milan,San Francisco,Mexico,Dallas,Beverly hills,Tokyo,Shanghai,Hong Kong.etc. Goyard bags and trunks are made from three plant fibres-hemp,linen &amp;amp; cotton. Goyard’s prime press strategy is silence. It forgoes any advertising, e-commerce, and celebrity endorsements,rarely grants any interviews and very occasionally makes products available to the mass market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Article IV: The Travis Scott Sneaker Lineup</title>
      <link>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blogs/blogs/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blogs/blogs/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>Travis Scott could make a compelling case for the most influential man in sneakers right now.While the size, scale or SKUs associated with his name don’t measure up to Mike, LeBron or his mentor Kanye, young La Flame has made sure to deliver the heat over the last few years with a slew of sneaker collabs.Originally signed to Reebok during his mixtape come up, his partnership with the vector did not make for any co-branded releases but did set the foundation for the endorsement work he’d do in the future with Nike, Helmet Lang and of course Jordan Brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Article V: The Adidas Yeezy Sneaker Lineup</title>
      <link>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blogs/blogs/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blogs/blogs/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Adidas Yeezy is a fashion collaboration between German sportswear company Adidas and American designer, rapper, entrepreneur and personality Kanye West. The collaboration has become notable for its high-end limited edition colorways and general releases offered by the Yeezy Boost sneakers line up. The collaboration has also produced shirts, jackets, track pants, socks, slides, women’s shoes and slippers. The first shoe model “Boost 750”.In 2020, sales for the sneakers reached nearly $1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Article VI: Cop the Culture</title>
      <link>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blogs/blogs/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blogs/blogs/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>India still lags behind having hyped sneaker stores such as Footlocker,Stadium Goods.etc.Whereas,there are sneaker stores from where you can buy deadstock or reselled shoes in India too but not all sneakers are generally in stock there. People like Anand Ahuja ,Vedant Lamba , Karan Khatri took the first step forward to spread the hype of sneaker culture in India and also opened their respective stores such as VegNonVeg,Mainstreet Marketplace.etc. Yeah,you can say they dont keep the most hyped sneakers but still they have pretty decent collectibles which you can cop to stay updated with the sneaker culture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog : Life Lately</title>
      <link>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blogs/blogs/chapter-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blogs/blogs/chapter-0/</guid>
      <description>To be honest life has not been only ups lately but adversity builds character and I believe whatever an individual has to go through has some purpose. To reach somewhere we urge to be at it takes sacrifices be it physically , emotionally or mentally. I have been working as a software engineer now for over 2.5 years and though it is an interesting field but its not something I would want to do for the rest of my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blogs/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blogs/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone.My name is Prantik Choudhary. I originally hail from Jamshedpur,the steel city of India aka “The land of the Tatas”.I started to write code when I was in the 6th grade,it was simple Java code in a BlueJ environment at that time.Since time passed by I learnt C++,mySql,Markdown but still Java and C++ remain the languages I still prefer to work in. I generally post random stuff here related to apparel,sneakers,hyped brands and other products that I am very captivated about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact me</title>
      <link>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blogs/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prantikchoudhary.github.io/blogs/contact/</guid>
      <description> Your Name Email Address An email address is required. Message </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
